Praise the Lord!
Praise His holy name!
I am meeting pastors and leaders!
Mexico Pastors' Conference With Prophet T.B. Joshua
The message is not only for the pastors but also for the leaders.
And the anointing of God too!
Mexico Pastors' Conference With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Hallelujah!
The Book of Galatians 5:6.
Very very important.
Also 1 Corinthians 13:13.
I want to talk about this before we go into the issue why we are here today.
Which is the book of Ephesians 4.
It actually gives me sleepless nights when I see the level that Christianity is going
and we cannot differentiate the Christians from religious people.
It is difficult today to separate the Christians from religious people.
Because of our practices, we find it difficult to know who is religious and who is a Christian.
I will now take this little message 'Christianity is not a religion'.
It is not a religion.
Mexico Pastors' Conference With Prophet T.B. Joshua
For Christians, Jesus actually came from above to keep the relationship and fellowship between us and God.
We don't need to go there; He came.
Just because of the relationship between you and God and our fellowship.
Christianity is not a religion but a love relationship.
Mexico Pastors' Conference With Prophet T.B. Joshua
That is why many of us today, we miss it.
We practice some teachings religiously.
When I say, some teachings religiously - without a loving relationship.
It is not a loving relationship if I stand here and fail to preach love;
we would continue to cause disunity, hatred and conflict amongst the Body of Christ.
Imagine if I was here preaching hatred,
telling you that place is not good, that religion is not good. No, we are not to judge.
If we judge now, who will judge us on the last day?
If I turn to be a judge, who will judge me on the last day?
Yes.
Christianity is not a religion but a loving relationship.
Mexico Pastors' Conference With Prophet T.B. Joshua
It is all about, "I love you and I love God"
I love God and I love you.
Hallelujah.
When you look at your life today, you will agree with me that your life is measured by your love for God.
Your life is measured by the love you have for God and for your fellow human beings.
Faith without love is faithless.
If you have faith without love, your faith cannot work.
That is why many of us today have a hard time using our faith.
In Galatians 5:6, Paul emphatically stated that faith works by love.
If faith works by love, it means one must possess these two.
The possession of both faith and love will motivate us to love God and our fellow human beings.
Without love, no matter how big your faith is,
you will only have passion for God, desire for God and an encounter with Him.
You cannot put love as passion or desire.
That is it.
Faith is faithless without love.
A person who does not love cannot be entrusted with the grace of God to heal, to deliver, to bless.
It is not possible for anyone without love to heal, in the name of Jesus.
It is not possible for anyone to deliver without love.
Because without love, it will become a personal gain.
When you don't love, you can collect money from anybody.
Even if a person is sick or dying, you would ask for money before praying for the person.
Without love.
Without love, money can come from anywhere.
Without love, you don't mind the source of money -
faith is faithless.
We ministers of God here today, I want to tell you, it is not possible.
Without the possession of both faith and love, you cannot go anywhere with God.
Take note of that.
You can see the hindrance you are having when using you faith.
Hallelujah.
I am taking you to the book of Ephesians for today's message.
The book of Ephesians 4.
Unity in the body.
Once again, it is all about love.
"Therefore, I, a prisoner for serving the Lord,
beg you to lead a life worthy of your calling,
a life worthy of your calling..."
Ask your neighbour, "What is your calling?"
Thank you.
If you are to live a life worthy of your calling,
if that calling is from God,
the most important aspect in your life to God is love.
Mexico Pastors' Conference With Prophet T.B. Joshua
If you are to live a life worthy of your calling,
and that calling is from God,
you are what you love
and your life is measured by your love to God and your fellow human beings.
Mexico Pastors' Conference With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Whatever your profession flows out of your relationship with Jesus.
Are you a pastor or whatever your calling flows out of your relationship with Jesus.
Mexico Pastors' Conference With Prophet T.B. Joshua
If you desire greater things, you need a greater relationship.
Verse 30.
"And do not bring sorrow to God's Holy Spirit..."
Our heart is the contact point for the Holy Spirit.
But the question is, "Is your heart free?"
As you are sitting, you need a free spirit.
Are you free?
Are you free from your past?
From where you are coming from?
Are you still in the present or in the past?
A free spirit is sensitive to God;
it can contact God, it can attract God.
We receive here free spirit.
Are you free?
Mexico Pastors' Conference With Prophet T.B. Joshua
"...Remember, He has identified you as His own,
guaranteeing that you will be saved on the day of redemption.
Get rid of all bitterness..."
I have been to so many pastors and leaders' conferences
and I have seen the Spirit of Father descend but did not remain.
Mexico Pastors' Conference With Prophet T.B. Joshua
He does not remain when He is grieved.
That the Spirit of God will not descend here today - no!
It's hundred percent guaranteed but the question is, "Will that Spirit remain in you?"
Mexico Pastors' Conference With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Because of pride and arrogance - our past life. Many are still living in the past as we are talking now.
When the Spirit of Father comes, He wants to be Himself in us.
Did you know that? That is to be ungrieved.
To be ungrieved.
When He comes---
I am telling you because He is about to come now.
Mexico Pastors' Conference With Prophet T.B. Joshua
When He comes, He wants to be Himself in us.
That is, to be ungrieved.
Many of us are coming from falsehood, fear of failure, fear of false accusation,
longstanding grudges, unforgiving spirits.
There are so many people you cannot forgive.
Mexico Pastors' Conference With Prophet T.B. Joshua
When you look at the book of James 5:17,
Elijah became depressed because he was angry with God.
He was a man just like you.
Depression comes from longstanding grudges, spirit of pride, arrogance.
We pastors, you know there is no superstar in the ministry of the Holy Spirit.
Mexico Pastors' Conference With Prophet T.B. Joshua
The spirit of competition among churches - robbing Peter to pay Paul.
Competition; we are not running a race between churches.
When the Spirit of Father comes, He wants to be Himself in you.
Are you free?
Do you have a free spirit?
Nothing bothers you at all now as you are sitting down?
Those things that bother you put your spirit in bondage.
Will T.B. Joshua touch me?
Will this man pray for me?
Will I get healed?
Will I be anointed today?
How will I get free today?
Spirit of bitterness, envy and jealousy.
Mexico Pastors' Conference With Prophet T.B. Joshua
These are the things that grieve the Holy Spirit.
He wants to remain in you and you to remain in Him
but because of all these---
The greatest battle seems to be the senses.
What you see, you desire it.
What you smell, you want to taste it.
Mexico Pastors' Conference With Prophet T.B. Joshua
This is my fear now, you have to be free before I come into your midst.
You have to release yourself! Rise up and begin to release yourself!
Rise up and begin to release yourself from that spirit of bitterness, unforgiving spirit,
where you are coming from,
those things that are bothering you!
Stand up and begin to release yourself!
So that the Spirit of God can remain and you too can remain in Him.
Open your lips and begin to release yourself!
What are you worried about?
What are you thinking about?
The Spirit of Father needs a free spirit.
Open your lips right now!
Mexico Pastors' Conference With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Release me Lord!
Make me Your vessel of honour.
Release me Lord from the spirit of fear!
Fear of failure.
Fear of false accusation.
Fear of sickness and disease.
Fear of setback.
Fear of limitation.
Fear of divorce.
Open your lips and begin to release yourself! There are many fears.
Release me Lord!
Mexico Pastors' Conference With Prophet T.B. Joshua
When you come Lord, I want You to be in me!
Begin to dump all the bitterness, malice, evil speaking!
Dump them!
Mexico Pastors' Conference With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Dump them - the spirit of anger, spirit of bitterness,
spirit of pride, arrogance,
malice, evil speaking!
Mexico Pastors' Conference With Prophet T.B. Joshua
In Jesus' name we pray!
Amen.
Mexico Pastors' Conference With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Hallujah!
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing Lives, Changing Nations, and Changing the World.
TT: Mel Flowers
RV: Pavel Tatyana Zheleznyakov 30/06/2018